all right here's a great question
particularly as testing sensitivity
increases in anti-doping
what is a picogram so a picogram is a
measurement of weight
an ounce is about 28 grams and a
picogram is a trillionth of a gram it's
kind of hard to get your head around
what that really means but if you take a
single cell
in your body and look at the weight of
the dna in that cell it weighs about one
picogram so this is a very small
measurement and when we look at the
concentration and the detectability of
substances in a urine sample it can be
measured down to the low picogram per
milliliter which is a concentration that
is extremely small
[Music]
you